Newton Yan

A passionate full stack web developer with 4 years of experience in creating high quality website and responsive web application. I have experience working with and have solid understanding in various web frameworks such as Angular and SvelteKit. Strong problem-solving skills and able to work collaboratively in a team environment. I'm eager to continue learning new technologies and adapting to new challenges.

yankaiyin@hotmail.com (647) 616-6144 www.newtonyan.com Toronto, ON, Canada

Education

The Chinese University of Hong Kong

B.Eng in Systems Engineering and Engineering Management | Sep 2015 – Nov 2019

- Second Class Upper Division
- Major GPA: 3.480/4.000

Awards and Honors

- Outstanding Students Awards 2019
- The Professor Julie Hung Hsua Yu Scholarship for Intellectual Excel-leration
- The Yen Scholarship for Academic Excellence

Work Experience

Belun Technology Company Limited

Programmer Analyst | Sep 2021 – Apr 2023

- Analyzed user requirements and designed solutions that meet their needs
- Developed web applications with Ionic (Angular) and SvelteKit
- Provided technical support and troubleshooting for existing web applications
- Enhanced and maintained company website
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams by leveraging tools such as JIRA

Automated Systems (H.K.) Limited

Analyst Programmer | Dec 2020 – Sep 2021

- Developed responsive web application with Vue.js
- Assisted in the development of the REST API using Spring Boot
- Collaborated with end-users to define application requirements

Programmer | Dec 2019 – Dec 2020

- Developed web application with Java and Apache Struts Framework
- Enhanced existing web application on .NET framework

Information Technology Services Centre, CUHK

Student Helper | Jul 2018 – Jul 2019

• Designed multimedia courseware using Adobe Premiere Pro, After Effects

Language

Cantonese (Native)
English (Fluent)
Mandarin (Flutent)

Skills

(Advanced)

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

TypeScript

SvelteKit

Angular

Tailwind CSS

(Intermediate)

React

Next.js

Express

MongoDB

MySQL

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Premiere Pro

Adobe After Effects

(Entry level)

Vue.is

GraphQL

Java

Python

Certificates

Professional Scrum Master II